Here we go... Upokami!
This time we have with us Utano Satoyoshi of Beyonce Seasonings
and Reira Ise of Angulum.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of the various artists
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
our recordings and rehearsals.
We'll be showing you the process of our recording, rehearsal and production.
I'm Reira Ise of upcami, and I'm going to show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
I'm Reira Ise of up-cam, and I'm going to show you the production process, including recording and rehearsals.
Yes, I am Yushi Sato, and the other day, Biophonic 2 was held,
Last year and the year before, Beyonce's was an event, but this time, for the first time, Japanese instruments were used in a concert with full orchestra arrangement.
This time, for the first time, Japanese instruments were introduced.
We are very much looking forward to the concert.
We are really looking forward to it, and the audience is also looking forward to it.
We are looking forward to it, and the audience is also looking forward to it.
I hope the audience will be looking forward to seeing him.
It's going to be great!
With an orchestra
Our group has never done this before.
It's very biophonic.
I thought it would be really interesting.
I've always wanted to try it, but I think it's because of the variety of instruments in the Bjorns' music that it's possible to do it.
I think it's fun to hear a fresh sound with the addition of instruments.
And I, Ise, I think it's interesting that Angelem is currently on a spring tour.
I'm going around the country on the “Secret Secret Secret” tour.
There are a lot of songs to dance to, so I reconfirmed my own choreography.
I reconfirmed my choreography, and I thought I should make my movements bigger since we were going to perform in a big venue.
I thought I should make my movements bigger since we were going to perform in a big venue, but I also thought that Angelem's songs are cool and their movements are big.
There are a lot of angular ranges that need to be enlarged.
But while making it bigger...
But I also want to make the dance bigger in one song.
But there are also choreographies where the dancers have to keep the dance within the range of the choreography.
It's very difficult to make the strength and weakness of the choreography
I was thinking how difficult it is to make the strength of the choreography, and we all worked together to make it happen.
I was asked to cover Angelum's “Urabara” at the festival on the same day, but it was already very difficult for me to keep the choreography together.
I was asked to cover Angelum's backside at the festival on the day of the festival, but it was already difficult for me to get it just right.
Let's start with this time's Up-Kami.
Mai Koseki, Tears for Tomorrow, Making of the music video shooting. Mai Koseki, Tears for Tomorrow, Making of music video shooting.
Now released on April 24th. Please take a look at the making of the music video for Tears for Tomorrow, from Mai Koseki's latest single.
Thank you for your patience. Please.
As the role of a normal girl who is in love as per the lyrics,
I'm a little cray-cray around here.
I mean, the world of this girl's mind,
I thought it would be nice if I could take a picture of a scene like this, which is far from reality,
I'm hoping to capture a scene like this, a little bit far from reality.
Here you can hear a normal show.
I'm hoping to do it from a standing position, in a really electrified state.
I'm hoping to do it from a standing position.
Okay, well, let's get started!
Yes, let's swing a little bit of power toward the sofa, MEME.
I'm Mai Koseki. Mai Koseki's solo debut single.
The shooting of the music video for Tears for Tomorrow has begun.
It hasn't been long since we started.
We're shooting from the image shot right now.
I'm shooting an image of a room where she is immersed in sadness while playing the lyrics about her boyfriend, who is no longer with her, or about him who is gone.
There will be some dance shots, so I'll do my best for the whole day.
me
Me.
I'm not gonna protect you with me me me me me
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid.
Laugh your silly ass off.
This place is like...
It's like an artist's shot.
It was a drama shot earlier, but here we're on a different stage.
But here it's on a different stage.
It's like Butel's coloring is done.
Okay, let's go to his place... with hands outstretched, tongue in cheek.
Don't hold it in your hand, tomorrow.
I'm already someone else's.
I'll be you in my heart.
I want to erase it, but I can't.I wanted to erase it, but I couldn't.
Obasagi Kimi Nowhere
Don't shake, don't shake, don't shake, don't shake, don't shake, don't shake
love is not chasing you, end up
I'm scolded
Is it raining? It's like rain is falling like tears
I only shot in the frame.
So hand movements are limited.
So you have to be careful about facial expressions and hand movements.
So, I'm trying to be careful with facial expressions, hand movements, and hand movements.
So, I'm trying to do a lot more movements.
I'd like to hone my skills even more.
I'd like to polish it up even more.
A sad premonition to love.
Let's play without making the wall of memories tie him to his place fiscal tears
I'm already someone's person
to the smile that seems to be bothering my heart
I want to, I can't erase it
Me and you and love, you and me, we're not
Thank you, you're not breaking me.
I can't protect you even if you scold me
I'll be high, and me and her will laugh, thanks to you, and I'll stay with you, Pei Jong.
I'll be back! Roll the camera, please!
I'll be ready...
where the walls of memory are only walls, a rebirth that binds
our rebirth, don't let it be tears, let it be tomorrow
I'm still all alone with my smile
A smile that looks good in my heart
I want to erase it, but I can't
It's just me and your love
You and me, me and me
Tomorrow is really music this time no water in my teary eyes so I'll hold a glass or something
Don't let it be tears tomorrow
I'm already someone else's person
A smile that breaks into my heart
I want to erase it, but I can't
I can't turn it off... my time, my you, my love, my dreams, my looking over, my meme...
me me
me
me me me me me Yes, the shooting of the music video for Tears for Temoro has been completed.
This was the first time for me to shoot a music video for a solo single, so I wasn't nervous.
I wasn't nervous, but I was told that my facial expressions were a little stiff at the beginning of the shoot.
But as we filmed, I gradually relaxed, and we did a lot of dancing,
I'm really looking forward to seeing the finished product now,
I hope that everyone will enjoy watching the film,
I hope you will all watch “Tears for Tomorrow” as much as possible.
I did my best. Bye bye.
Yes, I've seen it.
There are quite a lot of image shots.
I'm talking about the lip scene against the window and the image shots.
Country Girls' voice reminds me of Magnet.
even more mature and sad than then.
The refined expression on their faces is something that you can't help but be moved by.
I thought it was something that made me feel a strong attraction to them.
I was really attracted to it.
I've always thought that you are very good with tears and sad songs.
I've always thought that you are suited to tearful and sad songs.
It's a perfect song for you.
And the way the music video was shot
The way the music video was shot was very much like Ozeki-san's.
I thought it was really wonderful.
And as Utano said earlier
As Utano said earlier, there were a lot of image shots.
You have a very wide repertoire of images.
It's not just facial expressions.
It's not just facial expressions, but also the nuances of the hand movements.
I learned a lot from the wide repertoire of shots.
That's all for now, Mai Koseki, Tears for Tomorrow
This was the making of the music video shoot.
Let's try to be cheerful!
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 Making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 Making of Video
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024
This time, we will focus on the solos and shuffle units!
Let's take a look at 4.2.12.2.14.2.1
2.2.1
2.2.1 2.2.1
2.2.12 2.2.13 minutes later, I'll push it when I push it. Come on, then, 3 minutes later. Yes.
OK.
Okay. The first time I ever thought about someone, I was gently kissing a big affection.
I can't help it, after all.
I love you.
I've been right about everything so far.
I was so surprised that I won this year too, but even before I drew the lottery, I was so surprised that I won this year too.
But even before I drew it, I had a great feeling that I was going to win again this year.
I was just surprised that I got it.
I wasn't that surprised.
I didn't think I would win.
But it was with Eva, my classmate.
It was with Eva, so it was Eva?
So I felt really safe.
We've been going out to eat together a lot.
So I'm very happy to be able to work with her.
I'm sure I'll get some new kind of inspiration from you.
Oh, you want to dance from here, don't you?
Seino. Thank you for your hard work, music, I love you. I love you. I love you. I was surprised at my own voice, but all the members were so happy to see me and said they were looking forward to it.
I was surprised at my own voice, but the members were so happy to see me and said they were looking forward to it.
I didn't want to waste everyone's expectations and good luck, so I decided to work even harder.
I don't want to waste their expectations and encouragement, so I'm going to work even harder.
I tend to do a lot of “oriori” at live performances, but with this song, rather than shouting it out together, we all just shook our hands like this.
I tend to do a lot of “oriori” at live performances, but this song has an image of a sense of togetherness, so I thought I'd do my best.This song has the image of everyone waving their hands in this way, and that is a sense of togetherness.
I think it's a challenge for me personally to see how much I can create a sense of togetherness in the venue without using any kind of stirring up.
After the “BEYOND” block, I'm going to solo without a moment to catch my breath.
I'm going to solo.
I've been thinking about my solo a lot and practicing for it, but it's so cute!
I'm also going to perform a new song for the beauty pageant.
Which should I think about? I'm like, “Which should I think about?
But I'm going to perform in such a big venue for a lot of people.
And we're going to be broadcasting live, too.
I'm sure thousands and thousands of people will watch the show,
I don't think we will have such an opportunity, so I hope we can take good care of it and have fun at the same time.
This will be my third time, so I hope I can be somewhat prepared for it a little bit.
But I'm equally nervous, so...
I'll do my best.
A lie? No, no, you are lying.
You know about this?
After meeting myself.
I'm so happy every day, even today, you and Chido吗Different hassle, don't give up, lose it
Wrap your big eyes around me more, and I'll see you shrinking into white.
I can't get you out of my head.
Oh no!
I thought it was just a cover, my color, something amazing, I don't know if I can use this too, but it might be a little rude,
I don't know if I can use this, but if someone who doesn't know this song listens to it, they might think it's his song. I wanted to make it my own so that if someone who didn't know this song heard it, they would think it was his song.
In the previous year, I didn't know where I was going with my performance, but this time, with the presence of the powerful Yuki, I felt more relaxed than ever,
I think I was able to think about my facial expressions and various other things.
I was so nervous that I lost my nerve.
Thank you very much.
I was so nervous.
But to be able to do it properly with Eva...
I've never done it before in my career as an idol.
I'm in a different group, and it's not often that we get to do something alone together.
I was so nervous that I cried over my nervousness.
I was so nervous that I almost cried,
I knew that,
I was really, really weak with nerves,
But now that a junior member has joined the group, I thought I had to get stronger,Now that the juniors had joined the team, I felt I had to become stronger,
Eva supported me a lot, and I want to thank her,
I want to thank you for that, and I had a lot of fun working with you.
I saw that Kurumi Takase was performing solo for the first time.
Since it was Kurumi Takase's first solo, she had been gathering a lot of information from the members about what songs they would like to hear.
We talked a lot about what songs we liked and what songs we didn't like.
But the most important thing for me was the audience and the people who came to the show.
The most important thing was to choose songs that the audience and the people who came could enjoy together.
The most important thing was to choose songs that we could enjoy with the audience and the people who came to the concert.
We can see the audience from the back of the stage.
We can see the fenlight of the venue
I could see the fenlight of the venue swaying together.
I was really moved by it.
I was so happy for them.
Kurumi Takase.
Kurumi Takase had envisioned.
I was able to feel it too.
It was a wonderful stage.
I thought it was a wonderful stage.
And the duo of Yumi Kasai and Hisaki Ebata
Yumi Kasai and Hisaki Ebata
They are the same age.
I really felt like I was in sync with them.
I felt a sense of stability between them.
And the music selection was great.
I think the song selection was really good, but I don't think the three of us had much of a connection with Takase and the two of them.
I had never seen such a big interaction between them before, but I could feel their passion for the audience and for the show.
But even though Eva Takisaki was shaking a lot, she didn't seem nervous at all and gave a magnificent performance.
That's all for the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
Thank you for all your hard work!
This is the next video by Yuto Satoyoshi of beyonds and Reira Ise of Angerme.
Tsubaki Factory Power Flower Now is the time to be united Vocal Recording Tsubaki Factory's latest album
Vocal recording of Mizuho Ono from Tsubaki Factory's newest album “Power Flower: Now It's All One”.
Please take a look at the recording of Mizuho Ono's vocal from “Power Flower Now!
Okay, let's take some pictures. We'll go in blocks.
Let's do the first A melody. Take 1.
Okay, let's do the first A melody. Okay, let's do the A melody of the first verse. Let's do it like that.Please, let's do the A melody of the first number then! Take 1! Let's do it like that.
We want to make the most of that low part, so can you try singing it with that image in mind?
Next, we'll record the song in two parts.
Everything gonna be alright.
Let's do it. Whole group Whole religion
Let's try a little sister hamo. I can hamo.
Wholeheartedly assembled Wholeheartedly religious Wholeheartedly answered Everything gonna be alright.
Gonna be alright
Everything gonna be alright
All together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together, all together
OK, let's listen to this one.
Everything gonna be alright Everything gonna be alright Everything gonna be alright Everything gonna be alright
Everything gonna be alright
That's good.
You can count on me.
That's great.
I just took the subject line.
I haven't done the other side yet.
I'm sorry.
I've just taken the one with the most eye-catching player GO, so I hadn't done the other side yet. The episode is about a hotchpotch, camellias, hanami, everything that's not close, everything is fine.
Everything is fine.
I hope it's not too bad.
Who is it? It's like...
Who are you? Like, “Who are you?
I don't know who you are. It was funny.
It was a little bit.
It's just now that we're getting together... and I got a little cute.
It's a gathering.
We're having a gathering right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's take it a little lower, just there one more time.
Okay.
We're in the middle of something.
Okay, let's try the B melody. Okay, let's try the next B-melody
Yes, fireworks alright, camellia, hanamichi, everything that decorates is all right
the overlapping power is toward the blue sky
The figure is dignified and graceful
Beautiful all over the world
I like the second half.
I didn't mean to say the first line should be sung a little briskly
I feel like I'm making it up as I go along.
It's like you're trying too hard.
I want it to sound a little more natural.
The voice of the water is okay... and the chorus is dignified and graceful
Beautiful, I want it to bloom all over the world
I can't think of my dream alone
It's okay if it's a little more fresh and chic
I don't want it to be too rock 'n' roll
And a little more rhythm on the back.
Tighten it up as much as possible.
The figure is dignified, graceful, beautiful, as tight as possible, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Okay, we'll start the rap part here at the end of the chorus.
Okay, now take one
Red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red more red
Now is the time to become one eye, unite your feelings and move forward
Power Blower to a place I've never seen before
Now is the time to be as one, to move forward with all our hearts together, to a place you've never seen before, Power Blower
Didn't you just now say you've seen it both ways?
You've seen it, haven't you?
The coat and the coat are reversed. Both are reversed.
I've never seen that. I've never seen that.
I was almost fooled by the fact that you're the one who's going to keep doing what you're doing, but now it's time to come together as one.
Now it's time to come together and move forward
To a place I've never seen before
Power Flower
Now is the time to come together
We're moving forward as one
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
OK, we got it!OK, I got it!
I got them all! We're done!
Okay, thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Yes, I saw the vocal recording.
I really like your voice, Mr. Ono.
I don't know how to say it.
It's very powerful, but
I like your personality and the quality of your voice.
I think your voice is like that, too, but it's very gentle.
I think she's very strong, but even though she's strong, she's still full of kindness.
This song also has strong parts and fragile parts.
I think this song has a strong part and a fragile part too, but I don't know how to say it.
I think this song has a strong part and a fragile part, but they both go well together.
I thought it was really cool.
Your voice is so rich.
It's so rich.
Like what you often hear from voice trainers
I often hear from voice trainers
I was thinking as I listened to her that she has a richness to her voice
The gap between the A melody, the B melody and the chorus is really nice.
The director often tells me to make it sound a little bit badass.
I'm often told that when I shoot the gap and take the gap, I'm often told that I have a cool, rich voice and a delicate chorus.
But it's nice to be able to listen to both the cool rich voice and the delicate chorus.
I think it's really great that you can listen to both of them.
I thought it was a great technique.
This was the vocal recording of Mizuho Ono!
Let's get closer and together, and do our best tomorrow!
Now, it's time for Utana Yoshii and Reina Ise to say goodbye to you.
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I was really impressed by Mizuho Ono's vocal recording.
I think Mizuho Ono's vocal recording was very impressive.
I was very impressed with Mizuho Ono's vocal recording, as I was with all the members.
Our own recordings
You don't know much about recording other than your own, don't you? You don't know most of the recordings except your own, right?
You don't get to see that.
I think it was very valuable.
Depending on the A melody, B melody, chorus, etc.
I think the image that I have in my mind of Mr. Ono is totally different from the one that I have in my mind.
The atmosphere was totally different from what I imagined in my mind.
I thought the gap between the two was really cool, and I would like to steal a lot of his techniques and learn from him.
As for me, I was really impressed by the music video shoot of Mai Ozeki.
We just recently shot a music video for our new song, and the atmosphere of each song is totally different.
The atmosphere of each song is totally different.
The ratio of image shots, the atmosphere of the dance shots, the silhouettes, and so on.
I was also impressed by the atmosphere of the silhouettes in the dance shots.
We are going to add more and more facial expressions and gestures to our repertoire.
Beyond is also becoming more mature.
I want to be as cool as Koseki-san in every kind of music.
I want to be able to make cool image shots like Mr. Koseki
that's what I thought.
At UpCami, I've had the opportunity to go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll be showing you what you don't usually get to see.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time, up-cam's partner is
Yuta Satoyoshi of BEYOND'S SEASONINGS and
and Reira Ise of Angulum.
Good bye!
Next time on Upokami
Maiyesu KosekiMaking of the music video “Sunny Forecast
and
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 will be revealed.
Enjoy!
Yeah.